<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
  <string name="title">Roller Coaster 3D</string>
  <string name="subtitle">A Thrilling and surprising ride</string>
  <string name="paragraph1">A roller coaster is an amusement ride developed for amusement parks and modern theme parks.

\n\nThe 360 video below shows the roller coaster movement.
  </string>

  <string name="paragraph2">The oldest roller coasters are believed to have originated from the so-called "Russian Mountains",
      which were specially-constructed hills of ice, located in an area that would later become St. Petersburg.[3]
      Built in the 17th century, the slides were built to a height of between 21 and 24 m (70 and 80 feet),
      consisted of a 50-degree drop, and were reinforced by wooden supports.

\n\nA toboggan-like sled was raised to the top of a track which consisted of hundreds of rollers.
      This Roller Toboggan then took off down gently rolling hills to the floor. The inventors of this ride,
      Stephen E. Jackman and Byron B. Floyd, claim that they were the first to use the term "roller coaster".

\n\n Many safety systems are implemented in roller coasters. One of these is the block system.
      Most large roller coasters have the ability to run two or more trains at once, and the block system prevents these
      trains from colliding. In this system, the track is divided into several sections, or blocks. Only one train at a time
      is permitted in each block. At the end of each block, there is a section of track where a train can be stopped if
      necessary (either by preventing dispatch from the station, closing brakes, or stopping a lift). Sensors at the end of
      each block detect when a train passes so that the computer running the ride is aware of which blocks are occupied.
      When the computer detects a train about to travel into an already occupied block, it uses whatever method is available
      to keep it from entering. The trains are fully automated.
  </string>

  <string name="source">Source &lt;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roller_coaster"/>Wiki;</string>
</resources>
